### Serhat Ismail Zunluoglu

Jr. Front-End Developer

Nationality: Turkish Adress: Gebze/Kocaeli Driver License: B

Mail: serhatismail12@gmail.com

Social Media: <a href="https://linktr.ee/serhatzunluoglu">https://linktr.ee/serhatzunluoglu</a>
Github: <a href="https://github.com/serhatzunluoglu">https://github.com/serhatzunluoglu</a>

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/serhatzunluoglu

### **SUMMARY**

Hello, I am Serhat İsmail Zunluoğlu, I am studying in the 4th year of Computer Engineering Department at Necmettin Erbakan University. I am trying to improve myself in the front-end field. I am interested in Html, CSS, Boostrap, Javascript and React and I'm trying to learn these technologies. I try to develop myself and gain experience by participating in communities and taking an active role in clubs.

### **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Computer Engineering** Aug 2020 - Present Necmettin Erbakan University, Konya/Turkiye

### **EXPERIENCE**

**Jr.Front-End Developer** Oct 2023 – Present *Invivo Software and Technology Inc.* 

I work part-time as a remote Jr. Front End Developer in this startup and we work with technologies such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, SASS and React. I worked with Rest APIs and developed mobile compatible interfaces.

## Intern UI Developer Aug 2023 – Sep 2023 Jotform

I was one of the 4 trainees who formed the jr.phoenix team under the phoenix team at jotform company. I am working as a UI Developer Intern in this team.

# Head of R&D Department and Apr 2022 - Present Supervisory Board Mirketgiller

As Mirketgiller, we organize events and webinars. We cooperate with companies, communities and different organizations. I work here as the Head of the Research and Development Department and the Chairman of the Supervisory Board.

Yurt-Time Sports Student

Ministry of Youth and Sports

Oct 2022 – Feb 2023

Oct 2023 – Jan 2024

In the Yurt-Time Sports Project at KYK Seydişehir dormitory, I assisted with students' permission, entry-exit procedures, and event organization. I worked on this project for 2 semesters, serving as Project Coordinator in the second semester.

Intern Aug 2022 – Aug 2022 Akım Metal R&D Center

At Akım Metal R&D Center Software Team, I first reinforced my knowledge about HTML and CSS. Then I tried to learn Javascript and Angular's structure.



### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

Social Assistant Mar 2023 - Present Kodluyoruz

I am a volunteer at Kodluyoruz. We organize trainings and game events on discord in long bootcamps.

I am Core Team Organizer of Google Developers Students Club Necmettin Erbakan University.

### PROGRAMMING SKILLS

### Programming Languages, Technologies, Libraries and Frameworks

JavaScript, Python, C++ React, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, SASS Npm, NVM, Git & GitHub & GitLab

### HARD & SOFT SKILLS

### Software's

Visual Studio Code, ChatGPT, ClickUp

### **Soft Skills**

Teamwork, Communication, Problem-solving, Leadership, Creativity, Agile Methodologies, Public Speaking, Empathy, Stress Management, Presentation

### **LANGUAGES**

Turkish Native
English Professional Working Competence

### **CERTIFICATES AND COURSES**

### My All Certificates Click Here

**Software Factory | React.Js** Apr 2023

Üretken Akademi

**Hi-Code Front-End Workshop** May 2022

Kodluyoruz

### **PROJECTS**

**Software Factory Projects** Mar 2023 Projects I do on a weekly basis in the software factory program. <u>Click Here</u>